<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Scrolling Text</string>
    <string name="article_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="article_subtitle">What is Android Studio?</string>
    <string name="article_text">Android Studio is the official Integrated Development Environment (IDE) for Android app development, based on IntelliJ IDEA . On top of powerful code editor and developer tools, Android Studio offers even more features that enhance your productivity when building Android apps, such as: A flexible Gradle-based build system,fast and feature-rich emulator,a unified environment where you can develop for all Android devices,Instant Run to push changes to your running app without building a new APK,Code templates and GitHub integration to help you build common app features and import sample code,Extensive testing tools and frameworks,Lint tools to catch performance, usability, version compatibility, and other problems,C++ and NDK support,Built-in support for Google Cloud Platform, making it easy to integrate Google Cloud Messaging and App Engine.The core Android Studio IDE has been updated with improvements from IntelliJ IDEA through the 2017.3.3 release. Improvements include better control flow analysis for collections and strings, improved nullability inference, new quick fixes, and much more.Compiler and Gradle:-D8 is the default DEX compiler,The D8 compiler is now used by default for generating DEX bytecode.This new DEX compiler brings with it several benefits, including the following:-Faster dexing,Lower memory usage,Improved code generation (better register allocation, smarter string tables),Better debugging experience when stepping through code.Simplified output window:-The Gradle Console has been replaced with the Build window, which has Sync and Build tabs.Thread View in the Network Profiler:-After selecting a portion of the timeline in the Network Profiler, you can select one of the following tabs to see more detail about the network activity during that timeframe:Connection View and Thread View.Layout Editor:The Palette in the Layout Editor has received many improvements:-Reorganization of categories for views and layouts,New Common category for views and layouts, which you can add to with a Favorite command,Improved search for views and layouts,New commands for opening documentation for a specific view or layout element.You can use the new Convert view command in the Component tree or design editor to convert a view or layout to another type of view or layout.Run and Instant Run:The behavior of the Use same selection for future launches option in the Select deployment target dialog has been made more consistent. If the Use same selection option is enabled, then the Select deployment target dialog opens only the first time that you use the Run command until the selected device is no longer connected.When targeting a device running Android 8.0 (API level 26) or higher, Instant Run can deploy changes to resources without causing an application restart. This is possible because the resources are contained in a split APK.For more information refer www.google.com.\n\n</string>
</resources>
